<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>API-Docs</title><link>https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/</link><description>Recent content on API-Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/channels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/channels/</guid><description>Channel Changes # Using graphQL subscriptions we can listen for changes to a channel without making repeated queries! Before starting this tutorial you should understand basic graphQL and have a method of authentication. Completing our websocket tutorial will also be helpful.
Need authentication? Start with access tokens
Websocket tutorial can be found here
Selecting a Channel # Before we can subscribe to a user we need a channel ID.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/followers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/followers/</guid><description>Follower Alerts # This is a tutorial for follow alerts. This guide assumes you have a client ID or an access token from a user. You should also have a websocket connection open from this tutorial. Having basic GraphQL knowledge would also be helpful.
New to GraphQL? This tutorial explains the basics. https://graphql.org/learn/schema/
Building the Subscription # Follow alerts are made of a standard subscription. The streamer ID of the channel that you want to have alerts for is required.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/subscribers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/subscribers/</guid><description>Subscriber Alerts # The Glimesh API does not have a live update event for channel subscribers. However, you can listen for the subscriber chatmessage to be notified when someone subscribes to a channel. This requires that you have a working websocket connection.
Listening for Subs # Simply ask Glimesh for the added property in a chatmessage subscription. This is a deprecated property and will be replaced in the future.</description></item><item><title>Live Updates Explained</title><link>https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/explanation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://glimesh.github.io/api-docs/docs/live-updates/explanation/</guid><description>Live Updates # Live updates allow you to listen for changes through the API. Glimesh will notify you when a requested event occurs.
Live updates are sent via a websocket connection. You can set that up here.
Types of Events # There are 3 events you can subscribe to. Each works the same way.
Channels # Channel events occur when a top level field changes. You can listen for the status (live/not-live), title, and any other information.</description></item></channel></rss>